absolute-snow.co.uk 2016-03-17

# The Absoute-Snow Privacy Policy

The Boarding Company Limited considers user privacy and data protection to be of high importance and complies with the Data Protection Act 1998 in relation to the processing of data supplied to us by users and other personal data in our possession for any reason. The Boarding Company Limited records information provided by customers who complete account registration, who make a purchase on our websites and by the use of cookies. Our policy on COOKIES can be read HERE. We also record information provided to us by means of e-mail, conventional mail, telephone, fax, text messages, market research surveys and other means. We are committed to providing the highest levels of security to fully protect your online shopping experience. We use secure socket layer (SSL) technology. All payment information you provide is fully encrypted so that it cannot be read by third parties.

**Private Information**  
No staff at The Boarding Company Limited are able to see any of your credit or debit card information. This information is held by Sage Pay, our payment providers. Sage Pay are the UK’s largest provider of online credit and debit card processing services. When we provide refunds to your card, we cannot see any of your card information at this time either. This makes purchasing online with The Boarding Company Limited's websites far more secure than any in-store, mail order or telephone purchase.

**Transaction Security**  
All transaction information passed between The Boarding Company Limited's websites and Sage Pay is encrypted using 128-bit SSL certificates. No cardholder information is ever passed unencrypted and any messages sent to our servers by Sage Pay are signed using MD5 hashing to prevent tampering. You can be completely secure in the knowledge that nothing we pass to the Sage Pay servers can be examined, used or modified by any third parties attempting to gain access to sensitive information.

**Encryption and Data Storage**  
Once on the Sage Pay systems, all sensitive data is secured using the same internationally recognised 256-bit encryption standards used by, among others, the US Government. The encryption keys are held on state-of-the-art, tamper proof systems in the same family as those used to secure VeriSign’s Global Root certificate, making them all but impossible to extract. The data Sage Pay hold is extremely secure and is regularly audited by the banks and banking authorities to ensure it remains so.

**Sage Pay Links to Banks**  
Sage Pay has multiple private links into the banking network that are completely separate from the Internet and which do not cross any publicly accessible networks. Any cardholder information sent to the banks and any authorisation message coming back is secure and cannot be tampered with.

**Sage Pay Employee Access**  
No individuals within Sage Pay are able to decrypt transaction information or cardholder data. Sage Pay systems only allow access to their most senior staff and only in extenuating circumstances (such as investigations of Card Fraud by the Police). Your transaction information and customer card information is secure even from Sage Pay’s own employees because their systems never display the full card numbers, even on administration screens.

**Secure Website**  
Internet Explorer users go to Tools / Internet Options / Advanced and check the SSL2 and SSL3 boxes. Your browser will confirm that you are shopping in a secure environment by showing a locked padlock icon or an image of a key in the bar at the base of your screen. For Netscape users, click the ’security’ icon on the tool bar and check the SSL2 and SSL3 boxes.

Recorded information will be used to enable the fulfilment of purchase orders, the analysis of aggregated buying patterns and shopping behaviour and for our own marketing purposes. All direct marketing communications will be accompanied will be accompanied by an ‘opt-out’ option.

We do not supply, sell, trade, lease, loan or rent any personal information to outside organisations or individuals except when we have received your written consent for a product or service you have requested, or we are required by law to disclose details in the form of court orders or legal processes.

All the information you provide will be stored and processed in the United Kingdom. The personal information that we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security and The Data Protection Act 1998.

The Boarding Company Limited websites have links to other websites and accepts no responsibility for the privacy policies or practices of these other websites.

Your IP may be recorded when you visit The Boarding Company Limited's websites. This information is used to analyse website traffic and will not be made available to any individual or organisation, unless required by law.

The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by writing to us. We will require proof of your identity before releasing any data. We will provide the information at a charge of £10.00 payable with your request. In instances where you find information that we hold about you to be inaccurate we will correct or delete it promptly. We reserve the right to refuse to provide a copy of any personal data held, but will give reasons for our refusal.
